### Jee Hae Moon

438-503-5184 • jeehae.moon@gmail.com

#### **PROFILE**

A self-learning and motivated worker who takes responsibility on the given tasks. Versatile skill set with experience in **production planning, manufacturing scheduling and production data management**. Proven ability to organize and manage multiple priorities and achieve quantifiable results while driving collaborative projects forward.

## **EDUCATION**

### Bachelor of Engineering, Mechanical Engineering Internship Program

2014 - 2019

McGill University, Montreal, Canada

CGPA: 3.61/4.0

# **Health Sciences DEC, CEGEP**

2012 - 2014

Marianopolis College, Montreal, Canada

#### **SKILLS**

Software: SAP, PTC Windchill, Autodesk Inventor, CATIA V5, Solid Works, Abaqus (FEA software), MS Office Suite

**Programming:** JavaScript, HTML, CSS, JAVA, C, MATLAB/Simulink **Languages (fluent in):** French, English, Korean, Spanish (intermediate)

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### **Production Planning Assistant**

September 2019-October 2020

Hyundai Motorsports GmbH, Frankfurt, Germany

- Schedule all customer racing car production (i20N, i30N, Veloster) with accordance to customer delivery dates
- Monitor production inventory data and raise Purchasing Requests according to remaining stock
- Manage and update the Production BOM for Hyundai Motorsports customer racing cars
- Release in SAP all parts and assemblies for newly development vehicles
- Follow up with the Purchasing department for part delivery schedule
- Schedule, prepare and deliver work orders to respective departments (Engine, Transmission, and Bodyshell department)
- Establish checkpoints on work-in-progress to guarantee accuracy of work performed
- Communicate with sales, workshop and warehouse personnel to generate a yearly production schedule

#### **Mechanical Engineering Intern**

June 2016 – December 2016

Mando America Corporation, Novi, Michigan, USA

- Engineering intern at an international car supplier R&D center.
- Supported basic design development tasks such as design of a brake caliper (housing and bracket) under direct supervision of the Brake Design Engineer.
- Participated in the assembly process of brake caliper sampling with the manufacturing department of the company.
- Translated cohesive reports and drafted manufacturing details from Korean to English to provide concrete design deliverables to engineers.

## **ENGINEERING PROJECTS**

# SAE AERO DESIGN EAST COMPETITION (Capstone)

2018 - 2019

- Designed a light weight micro UAV style aircraft capable of transporting high weight payload.
- Required 3D software (SolidWorks) and programming skills (CFD simulation and FEA analysis).
- Mastered different manufacturing methods (Hot wire cut, Laser cut, and CNC).
- Involved efficient time management skills to meet competition deadline.
- Participated in the SAE competition in March.